Introduction
Welcome to twominenglish.com. Teaching you English in two minutes or less.

In this lesson, we are going to learn about things you might say at a gymnasium.

Signing Up
Worker : Hello, welcome to the gym.

Charlie : Hello. I am interested in signing up for a membership.

Worker : Great! Do you want sign up for this branch?

Charlie : Yes. I also work in the city so I want to know if I can also work out there with a single membership?

Worker : Yes you can. You can work out at any of our gyms in the city.

Charlie : That's wonderful! How much is the charge?

Worker : The fee is $100 per month, but if you sign up for 6 months we give you a 20% discount.

Charlie : That sounds good. I will sign up for six months.

Working Out
Lucille : Hey Jimmy. I did not know you work out here.

Charlie : Yea, I do. What are you working on now?

Lucille : Today is my cardio and arms day. I am going to jog for a while and then work on my arms. How about you?

Charlie : I am working on my abs and legs today. I will be doing a lot of squats (ေအာက္ပုိင္းထုိင္တာ) and sit ups.

Lucille : Nice. Do you want to stretch together afterwards?

Charlie : Sure. I'll see you later. Have a good workout!

Playing Sports
Terrance : Hey Willis! Do you want to play basketball later?

Charlie : I would but it is raining outside.

Terrance : Let’s go play at the gymnasium. They have indoor courts.

Charlie : That’s a good idea. They have indoor tennis courts also.

Terrance : Yes, I play tennis too sometimes. They have a lot of racquets and nice courts.

Charlie : Yea, let’s play tennis instead.

Joining Classes
Lucille : Hello, I would like to sign up for some fitness classes.

Worker : Great! What would you like to do? We have a lot of classes.

Lucille : I am not sure. What kind of classes do you have?

Worker : We have a lot of dance classes, yoga, light weight classes and pool cardio.

Lucille : I think I would like to join the pool cardio and a yoga class.

Worker : We have a 7am pool cardio class and 6pm yoga class.

Lucille : Sign me up for both!